My name&#39;s Ketchup
And my name is Mustard
Together, we&#39;re Ketchup and Mustard
Cut.
I have seen into the future.
And I have seen
that today is a new day!
A day... full of girls.
Yeah!
Action.
I just wish...
I just...
Line.
Russians? What...?
Yeah. Oh.
You lie. Sorry.
Alright, then. I&#39;ll use my torch
to set fire to the chamber... cham...
I got this one.
Alright, then. I&#39;ll use my torts...
Alright, then.
Alright, then. I&#39;ll use my torch to...
You alright?
-Yeah, sorry.
-I know, it&#39;s hard. It&#39;s hard.
...frequency band to relay...
I love how I get it right
when we rehearse
-and then we shoot...
-Oh, motherfucker.
I don&#39;t know my line...
-Oh, it was so good for the camera!
-I know.
-Okay. What is his line?
No!
That&#39;s totally against the rules!
Did you just...?
I&#39;m sorry.
Sorry.
-Let&#39;s do it again. Alright.
-Yeah.
Go!
Your mom called.
She needs you home right away.
Is everything okay?
No, I don&#39;t think so.
It&#39;s your grandma.
That&#39;s...
Yeah!
No. No, I don&#39;t think so.
-Such a crazy season.
-Okay.
-Ready? You got this.
It&#39;s your grandma.
-What&#39;s wrong with you?
-I don&#39;t know.
It&#39;s your grandma.
-That word is so funny!
-I can&#39;t...
I can&#39;t do this.
Yeah, I liked that one, too.
I can... do it!
Is this a rehearsal or are we rolling?
Hell yeah. Hi, editors.
Priah.
Oh, I&#39;m sorry.
-Push harder!
-I&#39;m in here.
I can fit!
What&#39;s wrong?
Hey, there!
We&#39;re having an issue.
Now doesn&#39;t that look just...?
Oh, I&#39;m so sorry.
Sorry, the... the bottom came off.
It happened again, it just literally...
-I&#39;m so sorry, guys.
-Ready?
One, two, three. And...
I have to go home.
Oh! Sorry!
What was that?
It&#39;s your grandma.
What?
Yeah!
Uh, David?